{
    "subject": "resource/University_of_Valencia",
    "predicate": "ontology/country",
    "object": "resource/Spain",
    "human_readable": "The country where University of Valencia is located is Spain.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.975257158279419,
            "question": "Name the country where the University of Valencia is situated."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9669082760810852,
            "question": "Is the University of Valencia in Spain?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9042770862579346,
            "question": "Where is the University of Valencia located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8807491660118103,
            "question": "Which country houses the University of Valencia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8080467581748962,
            "question": "What country is home to the University of Valencia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7888279557228088,
            "question": "To what country does the University of Valencia belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7655097842216492,
            "question": "In which nation can you find the University of Valencia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7041494846343994,
            "question": "What is the nationality of the University of Valencia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5666224956512451,
            "question": "If you wanted to study at the University of Valencia, what country would you travel to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.410617470741272,
            "question": "Spain is the home of which university?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The country where University of Valencia is located is Spain.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8103_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If you wanted to study at the University of Valencia, what country would you travel to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8103_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the nationality of the University of Valencia?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8103_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In which nation can you find the University of Valencia?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8103_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8103_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8103_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8103_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8103_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8103_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8103_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8103_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8103_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8103_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8103_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the response to your query:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe documents contain multiple mentions of \"University of Valencia\" and consistently state that it is a university located in the Spanish city of Valencia. This information supports the triple statement that the country where University of Valencia is located is Spain."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the University of Valencia, including its location in Valencia, a city in Spain. Therefore, the statement \"The country where University of Valencia is located is Spain\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}